const CarQuestion = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question:"When was the first traffic light in the world set?",
        answers: [1925, 1914, 1910, 1935, 1920],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question:"When was the first traffic accident recorded in the world?",
        answers: [1825, 1803, 1769, 1855, 1900],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question:
        "How much does the most expensive car ever cost?",
        answers:["$ 5 million", "$ 6.3 million", "$ 8.7 million", "$ 7.5 million", "$ 3.2 million"],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question:"What is the record time that has been made to change the complete engine engine?",
        answers: ["1 minute 42 seconds", "1 minute 5 seconds", "55 seconds", "35 seconds", "42 seconds"],
        correctAnswer: 5
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question:
        "Which is the most expensive car in the world at the moment?",
        answers: ["Pagani Zonda Cinque Roadster", "Maybach Exelero", "Koenigsegg CCXR Trevita", "Lamborghini Sesto Elemento", "Porsche 918 Spyder"],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question:
        "What makes Volkswagen's most popular Passat, Polo and Jetta cars getting titles?",
        answers: ["the roses of the winds", "lakes", "rivers", "mountains", "personal names"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question:
        "How many cars are Toyota manufactured daily?",
        answers: ["4.500", "10.000", "7.500", "13.000", "11.600"],
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "What years did Karl Benz make the first car?",
        answers: [1835, 1856, 1866, 1844, 1870],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question:
        "The MTT Turbine SuperBike engine, one of the most expensive, and recorded in the Ginis's book is the record for the fastest and most powerful engine in the world. What is the price of this engine?",
        answers: ["$ 100,000", "$ 120,000", "$ 125,000", "$ 150,000", "$ 160,000"],
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 
        "What is the strongest jeep in the world?",
        answers: ["Jeep Wrangler", "Lada Niva", "Land Rover Range Rover", "Toyota Land Cruiser", "Mercedes G500"],
        correctAnswer: 2
    }    
]

export default CarQuestion;